const questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "Our sir teaches Mathematics………………English.",
  answer: "besides",
  options: [
    "across",
    "besides",
    "beside",
    "both"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: "Please, come………………the bathroom.",
  answer: "out of",
  options: [
    "out of",
    "over",
    "on",
    "in"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: "Please, don’t laugh……………those beggars.",
  answer: "at",
  options: [
    "for",
    "against",
    "at",
    "from"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: "Please, stop……..so many mistakes.",
  answer: "making",
  options: [
    "to make",
    "make",
    "making",
    "makes"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: "She…….her husband for 15 minutes.",
  answer: "has been beaten",
  options: [
    "is beating",
    "has been beaten",
    "has been beaten",
    "beats"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 6,
  question: "The rain comes……………..the clouds.",
  answer: "under",
  options: [
    "in",
    "near",
    "from",
    "under"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 7,
  question: "There are…………views on the issue of giving bonus t the employees.",
  answer: "divergent",
  options: [
    "independent",
    "divergent",
    "modest",
    "adverse"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 8,
  question: "He has………….people visiting him at his house because he fears it will cause discomfort to neighbors",
  answer: "stopped",
  options: [
    "curtailed",
    "requested",
    "stopped",
    "warned"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 9,
  question: "There is no place for………….in an accountant’s job.",
  answer: "errors",
  options: [
    "assets",
    "asserts",
    "errors",
    "duffers"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 10,
  question: "Some of the luggage…………..not yet arrived.",
  answer: "has",
  options: [
    "has",
    "have",
    "is",
    "are"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 11,
  question: "No sooner………..than the police handcuffed him.",
  answer: "did he come",
  options: [
    "he came",
    "did he came",
    "did he come",
    "had he come"
    
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 12,
  question: "We didn’t……………the programme to be such a huge success.",
  answer: "Expect",
  options: [
    "Accept",
    "Except",
    "Expect",
    "Access"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 13,
  question: "I suffer from no……………about my capabilities.",
  answer: "illusion",
  options: [
    "illusion",
    "doubts",
    "hallucinations",
    "imaginations"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 14,
  question: "The student’s aren’t prepared …………….the examination",
  answer: "to take",
  options: [
    "to give",
    "to listen",
    "to work",
    "to take"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 15,
  question: "Please don’t …………when I am talking.",
  answer: "interrupt",
  options: [
    "disrupt",
    "interface",
    "interrupt",
    "disturb"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 16,
  question: "It is not fair to cast……………on honest and innocent persons",
  answer: "aspersions",
  options: [
    "aspiration",
    "aspersions",
    "Inspiration",
    "adulation"
  ]
},
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "If …………….I would not lose temper",
    answer: "I were you",
    options: [
      "I were you",
      "I was you",
      "I am not you",
      "I am you"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 18,
  question: "One who hates woman is called………….",
  answer: "misogynist",
  options: [
    "philanthropist",
    "ascetic",
    "misogamist",
    "misogynist"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 19,
  question: " ……………….takes charge of a prison.",
  answer: "A warden",
  options: [
    "An editor",
    "An optician",
    "A detective",
    "A warden"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 20,
  question: " Kites………….in future also.",
  answer: "will be flown",
  options: [
    "fly",
    "will fly",
    "will be flown",
    "will flying"
  ]
},
// you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
// but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

//   {
//   numb: 6,
//   question: "Your Question is Here",
//   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
//   options: [
//     "Option 1",
//     "option 2",
//     "option 3",
//     "option 4"
//   ]
// },
];

export default questions;